&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我想让你试着回到过去，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: What I want
you to try to do is go back,
原来以前的codepen已经在全球范围内快速下载了。
turns out that codepen from before
has fast downloaded globally.
我想让你尝试的是
What I'd love you to try is for
加倍的条形图，尽量使用快速网点。
the doubling of the bars,
to try to use fast dot.
继续，我们把它分成两个函数。
Go ahead and
we broke it out into two functions.
我们遍历了这些盒子的整个阵列斜杠。
We ran through the entire array
of those boxes slash bars.
我们测量了它们，然后我们第二次遍历阵列
We measured them all, then we ran
through the array a second time and
都变异了。
mutated them all.
我们可以使用FASTON吗，它基本上是从几乎原始代码开始的
Could we use FASTON, which is basically
starting out with almost the original code
我们有，把它包装在度量中，然后当我们变异它时，
we had, wrap that in the measure,
and then for when we mutate it,
将其包装在faston.mutate中，让我们看看有什么不同。
wrap that in faston.mutate and
let's see what the differences are.